<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="lib/oscal-author.css" title="Simple" alternate="yes"?>
<?xml-model href="lib/oscal-checkup.sch" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="oscal-ui.css" title="Fancy" alternate="yes"?>
<catalog xmlns="http://csrc.nist.gov/ns/oscal/1.0" id="SP800-53A-template_oscal"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://csrc.nist.gov/ns/oscal/1.0 file:/C:/Users/wap1/Documents/Gitlab/oscal-tools/53A-editing/lib/oscal_catalog_schema.xsd">
    <metadata>
        <title>SP 800-53A OSCAL Scratch Template</title>
        <last-modified>2020-04-15T15:30:25.493-04:00</last-modified>
        <version>version 0</version>
        <oscal-version>1.0_Milestone2</oscal-version>
    </metadata>
    <group>
        <title>Grocery shopping</title>
        <control id="control2">
            <title>Parking Lot</title>
            <control id="control2.a">
                <title>Fire lane and pedestrian crossings</title>
            </control>
            <control id="control2.b">
                <title>Handicapped spots</title>
            </control>
        </control>
        <control id="control1">
            <title>Express Lane</title>
            <part name="statement">
                <p>No more than about fifteen items per customer.</p>
            </part>
            
            <part name="objectives">
                <prop name="method">interview</prop>
                <p>A customer may be asked how many items she or he has procured for purchase.</p>
                <p>A <em>customer</em> who admits to having more than about fifteen items, can be
                    asked if they would please use another line.</p>
            </part>
        </control>
    </group>
    <group>
        <title>Features of structured (XML) editors</title>
        <part name="summary">
            <ul>
                <li>Designed for <em>documentary data</em>, supports prose, running text, inline
                    formatting, lists and tables</li>
                <li>Editable, context-sensitive formatting and <q>false colors</q> (color-coding
                    semantics and relations) - this means that by authoring CSS, users can even help
                    design appropriate data models</li>
                <li>Outline vs details views; alternative presentations</li>
                <li>Validation of structures against defined models and patterns (both
                    OSCAL/standard, and local/custom)</li>
                <li>Consistency checking both in the background and at intervals (milestones)</li>
                <li>Automatic numbering and content generation; data regularization and
                    normalization</li>
                <li>Forms controls (checkboxes, pulldowns, date widgets etc.)</li>
                <li>Outlining, drag-and-drop</li>
                <li>Macros, hot keys, code snippets, refactoring operations</li>
                <li>Structural and semantic querying (such as <q>show me all paragraphs shorter than
                        50 characters long</q>)</li>
                <li>Integration with external processes (filters, crunchers, content
                    converters)</li>
                <li>A generic XML toolkit will support authoring in OSCAL when we want. The same
                    tool would also support authoring in any other XML format, including something
                    further tuned and optimized. Think about what your data could look like produced
                    in its own custom-fitted and outfitted tagging – then converted into OSCAL (or
                    what-have-you) on demand —</li>
            </ul>
        </part>
    </group>
</catalog>